Mohammad Hasnain

Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

mhasnain753@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/mohammad-hasnain-96573b1ab

Summary

I am a young tech enthusiast who tries to learn, develop and grow. I love to explore different technologies and build wonderful projects. I'm having a positive and growing mindset that helps me to excel in my role. I'm having good interest in the world of web development, especially Full stack MERN development and React Native. I have also practised and developed multiple projects in front end development. I love to design well researched user centric websites using React development.

Reach out to me for relevant opportunities and discussion, I am very excited to work with Startups building next generations solutions.

Email: mhasnain753@gmail.com

Experience



Core Team Member

Microsoft Learn Student Ambassadors Club Sukkur IBA University Mar 2022 - Present (7 months +)

***EEE Executive Committee Member**

IFFF

Oct 2021 - Present (1 year +)

President Sukkur Region

Iyouth Pakistan Aug 2020 - Present (2 years 2 months +)

Education

Sukkur IBA University

Bachelor's in Computer Science, Web Page, Digital/Multimedia and Information Resources Design Aug 2019 - Aug 2023

Sukkur IBA

Bachelor in Computer Science, Computer Science 2019 - 2023

Skills

Research • Engineering • Problem Solving • Computer Science • Microsoft Excel • Management • Communication • Leadership • Entrepreneurship • Team Leadership